http://www.wyoben.com/terms-and-conditions

Address
Wyo-Ben, Inc.
TERMS AND CONDITIONS
IMPORTANT: Please read the following and the Privacy Policy before accessing and using this Site.
Thank you for visiting www.wyoben.com. We hope that you will find this Site helpful and informative.
The following are the Terms and Conditions that apply to and govern your use of this Site. These Terms also incorporate our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any terms or conditions herein, or have any questions, before proceeding contact us directly at email@wyoben.com. By choosing to access and use this site, you are expressly agreeing to be legally bound by these terms.
Exclusive Terms. Please note that these Terms exclusively govern your access and use of this Site and do not alter or affect the terms and conditions of any other agreement that you may have or enter into with Wyo-Ben for any given product or service. The latter agreement will continue to govern that specific legal relationship with Wyo-Ben.
Changes to Site. In order to improve our service to you, we reserve the right to make changes in the access, operation, and content of this Site at any time without notice. We also reserve the right to make changes in the Terms and the Privacy Policy, so please check before each use for changes.
Copyright Notice. You acknowledge that, unless otherwise specifically designated, Wyo-Ben is the sole owner of all intellectual property rights to this Site and its contents, including but not limited to copyright protection for all content, including the design, layout, graphics, photos, format, and other visual elements of the Site. All ownership rights pertaining to the information and material contained on this Site, including but not limited to the Wyo-Ben name, logos, trademark, graphics, photos, images, audio, video, messages, files and content, are owned or have been duly licensed by Wyo-Ben with all rights reserved.  Site pages and content may be electronically copied or printed in hard copy for internal informational, personal or non-commercial use only.  Any other use without the prior written permission of Wyo-Ben is strictly prohibited. Personal information submitted will be treated in accordance with our Privacy Policy. Wyo-Ben makes no guarantee, representation or warranty that the content of this Site or its use will not infringe upon the intellectual property right of any person, nor that the use, transfer, reproduction, distribution, transmission, or storage of any Site content outside the United States is in compliance with the laws of any other governmental authority or jurisdiction which may be applicable.
No Warranties Provided. The information on this Site is provided for general information purposes only. While Wyo-Ben strives to provide timely, accurate and complete information, you may discover some inadvertent typographical, technical, factual, or other errors or omissions in the information provided. Please bring them to our attention at email@wyoben.com.  Wyo-Ben makes no guarantees, warranties or representation, express or implied, concerning the information furnished to you on or through this Site, or concerning the information you provide to us.
Compliance with all Laws. You agree that your use of this Site will be in compliance with all relevant and applicable laws and regulations. The information provided on and through this Site may be deemed in some cases to be controlled technology. It is your obligation to verify and comply with all applicable laws and regulations of the United States pertaining to any potential access, transfer and use of any information herein which may be deemed to be “controlled” as defined by law. Users hereby agree to defend, indemnify and hold Wyo-Ben harmless from and against any and all such damages and liability.
Site Security. Due to the technical uncertainties, Wyo-Ben is unable to make any representation or warranty that the content, information, or links in this Site are secure and free of data-processing errors, technical glitches, operational problems, interruptions, errors, bugs, worms, viruses, unauthorized third party access, or any other harmful elements. You remain solely responsible for the security and protection of your system.
Outside Links. For your information or convenience, this Site may contain direct links or hyperlinks to websites that are maintained by third parties. When clicking on such a link, you are leaving our Site. Wyo-Ben has no control over, does not endorse, and is not liable for, the quality, operation, reliability, compliance with laws, ethics, business practices, or content of such third party websites, or for any product or service advertised or provided therein. Any transactions with such third parties, including provision of your personal information, are strictly at your own risk. We expressly disclaim all liability arising from your access of and for the content contained within or through any such third party website.
Access Outside United States. If you are accessing this Site from outside the United States, you are doing so at your own risk, and you remain fully responsible and liable for familiarity and compliance with these Terms as well as with the laws, regulations, directives, codes, and rules of the United States, as well those of the jurisdiction from which you are accessing the Site, and any other applicable jurisdiction which may be involved in the access, transmission, routing, receipt, disclosure, storage or use of information on this Site, or any commercial transactions conducted on or through this Site.
Privacy. The use of your personal information given to us during your visit to our Site is governed by the Wyo-Ben Privacy Policy, which is posted on this Site and incorporated into these Terms.
Limitation of Liability and Indemnification.  You agree that Wyo-Ben and its affiliates, customers, partners, and their employees, officers, directors, contractors, vendors, suppliers, assignees, successors, insurers and agents, are not liable in any respect for any damages or loss of any nature which may occur as a result of your access and use of this Site. You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Wyo-Ben and its affiliates, customers and joint venture partners, and their employees, officers, directors, contractors, vendors, suppliers, assignees, successors, insurers and agents, for any costs, claims, damages, losses, or other liabilities arising from your use of this Site in breach of these terms or in violation of the law.
Applicable Law and Dispute Resolution. You agree that these Terms will be interpreted under the laws of the State of Montana. Any dispute or Claim which you may have arising from your access or use of the Site shall be first submitted in writing to Wyo-Ben within one month (30 days) from the occurrence of the event upon which such Claim is alleged to be based, or such Claim shall be deemed waived. Any Claim which has been properly submitted to Wyo-Ben which has not been resolved within a reasonable period time not to exceed six (6) months may be submitted to binding arbitration as an exclusive alternative to litigation. You expressly waive any right to bring any litigation in any jurisdiction again Wyo-Ben based on your access or use of this Site or under these Terms.
Thank you for visiting www.wyoben.com. If you have any questions, comments, or suggestions concerning this Site, we would like to hear from you. Please contact email@wyoben.com.
Last Updated: 03/26/2014
Â© Copyright 2020 Wyo-Ben, Inc. All rights Reserved.
Site Index |
Privacy Policy |
Terms and Conditions
